作为一个猎手我比你出色得多  更强大  更聪明
I'm a better hunter -- stronger,smarter.
我能把你唯恐避之不及的恶魔控制住
I can take out demons you're too scared to go near.
你知道我不是故意要说那些话的  对吗
You know I didn't mean the things I said back there,right?
只是中了海妖的咒语才这样的
That it was just the siren's spell talking?
当然  我也是
Of course. Me too.
那么  那么我们和好了
So,we're good? yeah,we're good.
好吧好吧  来吧  现在告诉我  为什么会有那样的三分球
Okay,okay,now,come on,you tell me -- why kick that field goal?
因为这就是橄榄球
Because it's called football.
不  应该说是充满奇迹的橄榄球  那个三分球让我爽歪了
No,it's called fantasy football,and those 3 points screwed me.
说真的  吉姆  你需要享受生活
Seriously,Jim,you need to get a life.
嘿  哥们儿  有零钱吗
Hey,guys,got any change?
没有  朋友
Sorry,pal.
把你们的钱包交出来怎么样
How about your wallets?
没问题  放松点儿  好吗
No problem. take it easy,all right?
快把钱包给我
Just give me the wallets!
冷静点  哥们儿
Hold on,man.
吉姆
Jim!
吉姆  吉姆
Jim! jim!
快去报警
Call 911 -- now!
吉姆
Jim.
挺住啊
Come on.
嘿
Hey.
别乱动  别乱动  哥们儿
Don't move. don't move,man.
我感觉良好
I feel okay.
你甚至都没流血
You're not even bleeding.
拉我一把
Give me a hand.
你现在怎么还会活着呢
How you even alive right now?
我也不知道
I don't know.
不  不  不  你是对的  这很明显有古怪
No,no,no,you're right,it's definitely weird.
好的  鲍比  谢谢
Okay,Bobby,thanks.
出什么事了
What's up?
鲍比在怀俄明州发现了什么
Bobby found something in wyoming.
有活干了？
A job?
可能是吧
Maybe.
一个小镇  过去的一个半星期里没有一个人死掉
Small town,no one's died in the past week and a half.
这就不正常了吗
That so unusual?
听听他们如何摆脱死亡的
Well,it's how they're not dying.
一个癌症晚期的家伙蹦蹦跳跳走出了医院
One guy with terminal cancer strolls right out of hospice,
还有个家伙让劫匪给崩了 毫发无损的离开了
Another guy gets capped by a mugger and walks away without a scratch.
崩在屁眼上了？
Capped in the ass?
警方说  詹金斯先生胸部遭到9毫米口径手枪的近距离射击
"Police say Mr. Jenkins was shot in the heart at point-blank range by a 9mm."
难道他肥的像个轮胎
And he's not a doughnut?
街坊们都说是个奇迹
Locals are saying it's a miracle.
好吧
Okay.
那背后一定有问题 对吧
It's got to be something nasty,right?
有人做了交易或是什么的
I mean,people making deals or something.
你这样认为吗
You think?
那还能是什么呢
What else would it be?
我也不知道
I don't know.
好吧  咱们出发
All right,get that to go.
走吧
Come on.
干嘛呢？
What?
你确定要我一起去吗
Sure you want me going with you?
我不知道为什么不和你一起去
Why wouldn't I? I don't know.
我不想去托你的后腿或是什么也不做
I don't want to be holding you back or nothing.
哥们儿  我说几百遍了那是海妖说的  不是我
Dude,I've told you a hundred times,that was the siren talking,not me.
我们忽略这一段好不好
Can we get past this?
你说的没错
Yeah,we're past it.
你们是说你们是写博客的
Now,you two said you were bloggers?
是的先生 flooredbythelord.com
Yes,sir. flooredbythelord.com.
博客里记的都是主的神迹
All of God's glory fit to blog.
一些镇上的人说
Some of the people around town are
说你所经历的是一场奇迹
Saying what happened to you was a miracle.
是的  历历在目
It was. Plain as day.
你怎么那么确信呢
How can you be so sure?
你还有其他的解释吗
How else do you explain it?
医生都不能
The doctors can't.
我的心脏里有一颗子弹  像个小水阀
There's a bullet in my heart,and it's pumping like a piston.
你如何解释呢
Well,how do you explain it?
说实话我不是谁的圣徒  也不是什么年度优秀老爸
Look,honestly,I was nobody's saint -- not exactly father of the year,
都不是
Either.
好吧
Okay.
但是那家伙给了我一枪我却没流一滴血
But when that guy shot me and I didn't bleed a drop?
我只知道主给了我第二次机会
I just knew the lord was giving me a second chance.
是这样吧
Is that so?
我觉得  像是有天使在保佑着我
I had this feeling -- like angels were watching over me.
我想你们是不会理解的
I wouldn't expect you guys to understand.
我们会去尝试的
Well,we'll just have to try.
你们不必勉强自己
You wouldn't have happened to have
你过去的一周在十字路口转悠过吗
Swung by a crossroads in the past week or so?
没有
No.
也许你遇到某个人...
Maybe you met someone...
是黑色眼球
With black eyes?
或是红色的
Or red?
你们说你们是干什么的来着
Who'd you guys say you were again?
没关系  谢谢你抽出时间
Never mind. Thank you for your time.
嘿
Hey.
有收获吗
Anything?
那个癌症生还者
That cancer survivor?
他临床诊断已经死了  他妻子拔掉的插管
He was clinically dead,his wife pulled the plug,
现在他在和他妻子庆祝20周年结婚纪念日
And now he's taking her out for their 20th anniversary.
-有做过交易的迹象吗  -没有
Any sign of a deal? No.
你怎么样  发现有什么死人吗
What about you? Found anyone dying around here?
科尔·格里芬斯之后就没有了
Not since Cole Griffith.
他10天前过世的
He dropped 10 days ago.
他是我找到的最后一个死人
It was the last death I could find.
那么你在想什么
So,what are you thinking?
也许他就是人们所说的
Eh,maybe it is what the people say it is.
奇迹
Miracles?
迪恩  以我们的经验  什么时候会有奇迹发生
Dean,our experience,when do miracles just happen?
这里头没有交易
Well,there's no deals.
这里没有宗教治愈师
There's,uh,no skeevy faith healers.
有些灵魂不能重见光明
I mean,these souls just ain't getting dragged into the light.
也许是附近没有载体
Maybe 'cause there's no one around to carry them.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
死神  是他们做的  对吧
Well,grim reapers -- that's what they do,right?
游荡的鬼魂？
Shlepp souls?
如果死神不在镇上  就没人死掉了
So,if death ain't in town -- then nobody's dying.
所以呢  本地的死神罢工了
So what? the local reaper's on strike?
玩九球台球去了？
Playing the back nine?
我不知道  萨姆
I don't know,Sam.
那我们找个也许知道内情的人谈谈
Well,then,let's talk to somebody who might.
我最后遇到的是个抱抱熊
Well,last I checked,huggy bear ain't available.
不  哥们儿  那个孩子  孩子？
No,dude,the kid. the kid?
那孩子绝对死透了
The kid's a doornail. exactly.
如果他是这里最后一个死掉的人
Look,if he was the last person to die around here,
也许是他看到了什么
Then maybe he's seen something.
我们应该和他谈谈
We should talk to him.
我喜欢你对那的解释
I love how matter-of-fact you are about that.
奇怪的生灵
Strange lives.
你确定这会管用吗
You sure this is gonna work?
不
No.
但是如果他的鬼魂在附近  这至少能驱走他
But if his spirit's around,this should smoke him out.
什么  这工作很狗屁  就是这样
What? This job is jacked,that's what.
怎么会呢
How so?
你要我赶走一个怪物或是焚尸  咱是做了好事
You want me to gank a monster or torch a corpse,hey,let's light it up,
对吧
Right?
但是这个
But this?
如果我们搞清楚的话  那些人就要死掉了
If we fix whatever this is,people are gonna start dropping dead.
无辜的人
Good people.
迪恩  我也不想他们死  但是大自然是有规律的
Look,I don't want them to die,either,Dean,but there's a natural order.
你没开玩笑  对吧  什么
You're kidding,right? What?
你没觉得这有多讽刺吗
You don't see the irony in that?
我是说你和我就像是大自然规律的传递者
I mean,you and me,we're like the poster guys of the unnatural order.
我们所做的就是传递死亡
All we do is ditch death.
是啊  但是常规对我们并不适用  是吧
Yeah,but the normal rules don't really apply to us,do they?
我们是如此的与众不同
We're no different than anybody else.
我被恶魔之血所染
I'm infected with demon blood.
你下过地狱
You've been to hell.
迪恩  我知道你想认为自己是管子工乔
Look,I know you want to think of yourself as joe the plumber,Dean,
但是你不是
But you're not.
我也不是
Neither am I.
你接受得越快你摆脱得越快
The sooner you accept that,the better off you're gonna be.
管子工乔是个蠢货
Ah,Joe the plumber was a douche.
你要帮我了结这一切吗
You gonna help me finish this?
嘿
Hey!
你们在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
只是...
Uh,just...
别紧张
Take it easy.
这是什么
What the hell is this?
这--这--这  不是你想象的那回事
Okay,this -- this -- this is not what it looks like.
是吗
Really?
看上去像恶魔崇拜仪式
'cause it looks like devil worship.
什么? 才不是!
What? no!
这决不是给恶魔崇拜仪式
No,this is not devil worship.
这--这--这个--呃--
This -- this is -- this -- this is,uh...
我不知道怎么答才好
I don't have a good answer.
好了  我们先走了
Look,we're leaving.
想走到哪儿去啊
You're not going anywhere...
想都别想
...ever again...
萨姆
...sam.
阿拉斯泰尔
Alastair.
我还以为你已经在油锅里炸得通透酥脆
I thought you got deep fried,extra-crispy.
只是个儿科医生的皮囊
Just the pediatrician I was riding.
他老婆还在满世界找他呢
His wife's still looking for him.
真搞笑
It's hilarious.
总之
Anyway...
没时间聊了
No time to chat.
过会儿还和死神有个浪漫约会
Got a hot date with death.
迪恩
Dean!
变强了啊  萨姆
You're stronger,sam.
是不是经常一个人躲着练习呢
You've been soloflexing with your little slut?
你不会了解的
You have no idea.
觉得怎么样
How you doing?
-怎么样了？-痛死我了
I'm in pain,that's how I'm doing.
估计是脑震荡了
I think I have a concussion.
要阿司匹林吗
You want some aspirin?
不用了谢谢  豪斯医生(同名美剧的主角)
No thanks, House.
恶魔  是吧
So,demons,huh?
好在有上天眷佑
Yeah. so much for miracles.
这次阿拉斯泰尔又怎么了
And what the hell happened with alastair again?
我说过了  他想把我扔起来  结果没成功
I told you,he tried to fling me or whatever,and it didn't work,
然后他就逃走了
So he bailed.
他为什么没能把你扔出去
Well,how come he couldn't fling you?
上次他可是轻而易举
He chucked you pretty good last time.
这我不清楚
Got no idea.
萨姆  帮我个忙
Sam,do me a favor.
你想把秘密放在心里  我也没办法
If you're gonna keep your little secrets,I can't really stop you,
但别把我当成个傻瓜 好吗
But just don't treat me like an idiot,okay?
什么? 迪恩  我没什么秘密啊
What? dean,I'm not keeping secrets.
随你了
Whatever.
你回去调查了个那个死去的孩子吗
So,did you go back and q-and-a the dead kid?
没必要
Didn't have to.
鲍比打电话过来了
Bobby called.
他做了些调查
He did some digging.
然后?
And?
他认为我是对的
He thinks I'm right.
这里的死神不见了
Local reaper's gone.
不仅仅是不见了  而是被绑架了
Not just gone -- kidnapped.
魔鬼干的? 为什么?
By demons? why?
听听这个
Listen to this.
"新夜之下  噬死神
"and he bloodied death under the newborn sky -- sweet to taste,
初尝味美且甘  咽后遂渐苦而涩"
But bitter when once devoured."
华丽  到底什么意思
Swanky. what the hell's that mean?
这是一个不为人知的事实
Well,it's from a very obscure,very arcane version of revelations.
和我想的一样吗
Which means what I think it means?
就是说  在冬至的夜晚杀掉一个死神
Basically,you kill a reaper under the solstice moon -- tomorrow night,
也就是明天晚上  你就解开了一个封印
By the way -- you got yourself a broken seal.
怎么去绑架死神? 死亡是不会消失的
How do you ice a reaper? you can't kill death.
不知道  也许魔鬼们就能
I don't know. maybe demons can.
我想知道  现在那些天使们躲到哪儿去了
Where the hell are the angels is what I want to know.
这回  他们倒是能帮上忙
We could use their help for once.
看来只有我们自己解决了
It looks like we're gonna have to take care of this one ourselves.
我们怎么做
What are we gonna do,
大摇大摆这么去救死神? 救那些和谐的街坊?
Just swing in and save the friendly neighborhood reaper?
你出主意吧  我洗耳恭听
You got a better idea,I'm all ears.
迪恩  死神是看不见的
Dean,reapers are invisible.
只有死人和垂死的人才能看到他们
The only people that can see them are the dead and the dying.
如果只有变成鬼才能看到的话
Well,if ghosts are the only ones that can see them...
然后?
Yeah?
我们就变成鬼吧
...then we become ghosts.
你还真是得脑震荡了
You do have a concussion.
有点疯狂  我知道
Sounds crazy,i know.
是很疯狂
It is crazy.
怎么做?
How?
不知道怎么说你们这两个疯子
I can't even begin to tell you how crazy you two are.
帕梅拉 您是我们的雪中之炭 黑暗中之光明
Well,pamela,you're a sight for sore eyes.
真是贴心啊  牢骚男
Aw,that's sweet,grumpy.
这话我这瞎子说  可有点讽刺啊
What do you say to deaf people?
哪根筋让你想到这么个灵魂出窍的方法
Which one of you brainiacs came up with astral projection?
是您啊
Yo.
你当然这么说  查奇(1974年情景喜剧《欢乐时光》的角色)
Of course. Chachi.
那么
So,
讲清楚--你们要让灵魂从身体里出来
Let's be clear -- you want to rip your souls out of your
然后在次元空间里面瞎转悠
Bodies and take a little stroll through the spirit world?
恩哼
Mm-hmm.
你们知不知道这有多疯狂啊
Do you have any idea how heavy-duty insane that is?
也许吧  但是死神在那儿  所以
Maybe,but that's where the reaper is,so...
所以  你们还是疯了
So,it's nuts.
别说的好像你不知道这事的本质似的
Not if you know what you're doing.
是你们不知道自己到底在做什么
You don't know what you're doing.
你知道就够了
No,but you do.
我的确知道
Yeah,i do.
你们晓得吗
And guess what?
被拉到你们这个关于天使魔鬼天堂地狱的交易里  我受够了
I'm sick of being hauled back into your angel-demon,soc-greaser crap.
我也希望不掺和  回家看看法官朱迪多悠闲
Look,i'd love to be kicking back with a cold one,watching "judge judy,
很好  还有关于瞎子的笑话吗
too. nice. more blind jokes?
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.
我们讨论的世界末日
We're talking the end of the world here,okay?
到时候  不再有流苏裤子  不再有雷蒙斯唱片  什么都没有了
No more tasseled leather pants,no more ramones cds,no more nothing.
我们需要你
We need your help.
天才们  告诉我
Tell me something,geniuses.
如果你们真的穿过帷帐  找到死神
Even if you do break into the veil and you find the reaper,
你们又要怎么去救他呢
How you gonna save it?
该怎么做就怎么做
With style and class.
你们到时候就是两片浮云
You're gonna be two walking pieces
碰不到也移动不了任何东西
Of fog who can't touch or move anything.
还没有防御力  两位高手
You'll be defenseless,hotshot.
我记得有一群鬼魂曾经把我们打得半死
I seem to recall a bunch of ghosts beating the crap out of us.
他们有的是时间练习
Yeah,they had plenty of time to practice.
这样  我们就得立即开始
Well,then,i guess we got to start cramming.
哇哦  英雄二人行
Wow,couple of heroes.
行了
All right.
躺下来
Lie down.
闭上双眼
Close your eyes.
Animum vult decipi,ergo decipiatur.
Vis,vis,vis.
好了
Okay,guys.
行了
That's it.
开始行动吧
Showtime.
怎么没有射太阳穴的感觉啊
Well,nothing like shooting blanks.
备用方案是什么
What's plan "B"?
感觉好像黛米摩尔
Oh,i'm so feeling up demi moore.
好了  估计你们已经上了彩虹
All right,so,I'm assuming you're somewhere over the rainbow.
记住  我到时候还要把你们弄回来
Remember,i have to bring you back.
我会在你们耳边念咒
I'll whisper the incantation in your ear.
你可是有一对翘臀啊
You have got a great ass.
她 她说什么
What'd she -- what'd she say?
这真劲爆
That was wild.
有没有感觉?
Am I making you uncomfortable?
快离开我的身体
Get out of me.
真是个玩不起的  走吧
You're such a prude. come on.
伙计  在这镇上我们已经飘荡了个把钟了
Oh,man,we've been spooking this town for hours.
没见着恶魔  没见着黑烟
No demons,no black smoke.
我说还是去维多利亚秘密偷窥那些女生吧
I say we hit victoria's secret and get our peep on,huh?
三点钟方向
Hey,hey,hey,3:00.
注意窗口的小孩
Kid in the window.
我没事吧  他在看着我们
Am I crazy or is he looking at us?
因为我们之前见过他
It's 'cause we've seen him before.
是吗
We have?
报纸上
Newspaper.
科尔 格里芬斯 这里死的最后一个人
Cole griffith,the last person to die in this town.
科尔?
Cole?
是妈妈啊
It's mom.
你爸爸说我疯了
Your dad thinks I'm crazy.
你在吗
Are you here?
有个相框掉了
A picture frame fell over.
我肯定那是你  宝贝
I could have sworn it was you,baby.
你还在我的身边吗?
Are you still here with me?
天啊
Oh,my god!
住手! 你怎么做到的
Stop! how are you doing that?
- 你们是谁 - 放轻松点 科尔 没事的
Who are you? relax,cole. it's okay.
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
可能不太容易接受  但是你已经死了
Look,this isn't gonna be easy to hear,but you're dead.
你是一个鬼魂  我们也是
You're a spirit. us too.
当然  谢谢了  海利·乔  我知道自己已经死了
Yeah,thanks,Haley Joel. I know I'm dead.
你们想干嘛
What do you want?
只想和你聊聊
We just want to talk.
聊什么
About what?
我每天清晨就出门了
I was outside all morning.
他们都会提醒我如果太冷了就得小心了
They tell you to be careful when it's cold.
因为冷空气会引发哮喘病
Cold air can cause an asthma attack?
但事情发生在我回到房间后
But then I was in my room.
那一切来得太快了
It happened so fast.
我大声叫妈妈过来  但始终都没人过来
I called out for my mom,but nothing came out.
接着就天昏地旋的  不久我就站在那儿
Everything started spinning,and then I was just standing there,
看着自己的躯体躺在地上
Looking down at my body.
也就是那时你看到了那个家伙
And that's when you saw the man?
太可怕了  那个大伯穿着一套黑西装
Creepy,old guy in a black suit.
他要我跟他走  但
He wanted me to go with him,but...
我不想离开
...i didn't want to go.
死神
Reaper.
你是怎么摆脱他的
How'd you get rid of him?
什么都没干
I didn't.
是黑烟干的
The black smoke did.
黑烟
Black smoke?
这儿到处都是
It was everywhere.
我跑到衣柜里躲了起来  等我出来的时候
I hid in the closet,and when I came out
黑烟和大伯都消失了
It was gone,and so was he.
那你知道那个黑烟去了哪儿吗
Do you know where the smoke went?
不知道
No.
但我能知道它在哪儿
But I know where it is.
他们回来了
They're back.
谁
Who?
其它的死神
Another reaper.
等等  我们想和你谈谈
Wait! we need to talk to you!
迪恩
Dean.
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
我们交情可深着呢
We go way back.
你不记得了吗
You don't remember me?
说实话  如果每次女孩子对我这么说就有5分钱的话
Honestly,if I had a nickel for every time I heard a girl say that...
至少你得给我点儿提示吧
You're gonna have to freshen my memory.
泰莎
Tessa.
那是我其中一个名字  想起来了
That's one of my names,yeah.
你真得认识她
So,you do know her.
就是那次车祸去得医院里
From the hospital after the accident.
和老爸一起那次吗
The accident with dad?
那么说  这个死神是追你的那个
So,this is the reaper that came after you.
是的
Yeah.
这个笑话很冷
Well,this was fun.
-好了  你说完了的话我就失陪了  -等等  先等一下
- Now,if you'll excuse me - wait,wait,wait,wait,
你不能  不能带走这孩子
You can't -- you can't take the kid.
为什么  这个镇上到处都是恶魔  这就是原因
Why? demons are in town,that's why.
他们已经抓走了你的一个同族
They've already snatched your reaper pal.
-那个孩子知道你同族的下落  -那又怎么样呢
- The kid knows where. - so?
所以  你应该马上离开
So,you should shag ass.
因为就我们所知  他们绝对会再来抓你
For all we know,they could try and snatch you,too.
只不过这个镇就这里有问题
Except that this town is off the rails,
而有人正在努力解决这个问题
And someone has to set it straight.
对  我们当然明白  但是目前的情况有点特殊
Yeah,we understand that,but these are special circumstances.
什么情况  你的天使和恶魔在这儿开战了吗
What? your whole angel-demon dance-off?
我可不在乎
I could care less.
我只来做我该做的事
I just want to do my job.
当然  我们可以帮你完成你的工作
Right,yeah,and,look,we want to help you do your job.
-只希望你能先离开  -不
- So,if you would just bail town. - no.
那你能不能等我们把事儿解决了之后再带走那孩子
Well,then,could you hold off until we fix this?
求你了
Please.
好吧  但是先把话说清楚
All right,but just so we're clear,
事情一旦解决了  那么这个孩子就归我了
When I start reaping again,I'm starting with the kid.
明白
Understood.
我去找他
I'll find him.
等下  先等等
Wait,wait,wait,wait.
你打算怎么跟他说呢
What are you gonna say to him?
尽我所能吧
Whatever I have to.
这一切一定让你万全不知所措  对吗
This all must be pretty overwhelming,huh?
更让你惊恐不已
Pretty scary,too.
我妈妈才是最难受的
The worst is my mom.
看到她这样心理一定很难受吧
Must be hard seeing her like this.
她每天都会来我房间  和我说话
She's always coming in here,talking to me,
告诉我她有多伤心
Telling me how sad she is.
我故意弄翻东西想告诉她我在这儿
I knock some stuff over to let her know I'm here,
但那却让她更加地伤心了
But she only gets sadder.
也许你应该让足球飞得慢些
Well,you might want to ease up on the flying soccer balls.
我不会告诉你那些黑烟在哪儿
I'm not telling you where the smoke is.
那如果我告诉你只要你帮了我
What if I told you that if you helped me...
你就可以留下来  而且是永远的呢
You wouldn't have to leave here -- ever?
哪搂下那个死神呢
What about the one downstairs?
泰莎吗  她不会来打扰你的
Tessa? oh,she wouldn't bother you.
其它死神也不会再来了
No reaper would.
你可以和你的家人在一起
You could just stay here with your family
想陪他们多久都行
For as long as you wanted.
你说真的吗
You can do that?
当然  没问题的
Yeah,you bet I can do that.
你发誓
You swear?
我发誓
I swear.
命运真是有趣
I'll tell you,life is funny.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你和我  又相遇了
You and me -- together again.
你不会  不会是想打我的主意吧
Are you -- are you making a move on me?
你是唯一一个逃过此劫的人  迪恩
You're the one that got away,Dean.
知道这种发生几率有多甚微吗
You'd be surprised how little that happens to me.
可以帮我保守一个秘密吗
Can I tell you something between you and me?
我还能跟谁说去
Who am I gonna tell?
在我们俩那次经历之后
After our little,uh,experience...
有整整一年时间  我都觉得
For that whole year,I felt like I had this...
我的内心深处总有所空缺
Hole in my gut...
就像是我错失了什么
Like I was missing something.
我一直不知道究竟是什么
I didn't know what.
知道那是什么吗
Do you know what it was?
就是你
It was you.
与父亲和萨姆生离死别的那种痛比起来
The pain of losing my father and sammy.
我只是
I just...
我真希望能永远和你呆在一起
I wish I had gone with you for good.
但现在我完全不会在那么想了
But I guess things are different now.
为什么
What?
就因为你有天使庇护吗
The angels on your shoulder?
看来你也知道了  对吗
So,you know about that,huh?
噢  你误会了
Well,hey,don't get me wrong.
我见过的那些个翅膀男大多都很混蛋
I mean,most the ones I've met are dicks with wings.
但是
But still...
对于我所做过的那些事
You know,I've done things.
那些令人发指的的事
Horrible things.
而那些家伙却仍然给了我第二次机会
And someone upstairs still decided to give me a second chance.
那真得让我觉得
It just makes me feel...
我也无法说清
I don't know.
伙计们
Hey,guys.
嘿  科尔
Hey,Cole.
我叫泰莎
I'm Tessa.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not going to hurt you.
没事的  科尔  就把你刚刚对我说的告诉他们
It's okay,Cole. just tell them what you told me.
我在我的葬礼上见到了黑烟
I saw the black smoke at my funeral.
在公墓里
At the cemetery?
是在殡仪馆
At the funeral home.
那里到处都是
It was everywhere.
你干的吗
You doing that?
不是
No.
泰莎
Tessa!
科尔  你没事吧
Cole,you okay?
我们该怎么去对付这东西
Well,how the hell are we supposed to fight that?
-我也不知道  得学会灵动才行吧  -今晚之前学会
- I don't know. learn some ghost moves? - by tonight?
好的  没问题  你有一副宫本先生的之态了
Yeah,sure. I'll meet you back at Mr. Miyagi's.
宫本是谁啊
Who's Mr. Miyagi?
你要集中念力才能移动它
It's not gonna move if you don't concentrate.
我正在集中呢
I am concentrating.
噢  转起来吧  宝贝
Ah,here we go,baby.
就坚持了那么一下
You pull a muscle?
好吧 尤达大师  让我们见识下你的本事
All right,Yoda,let's see what you got.
伙计
Dude!
你这够灵异的
You are so amityville.
这根本不算什么
This isn't even the good stuff.
看到了吗  如果你想揍某人的话
See? if you want to hit something,
-只要带点火气就行了  -嗯哼  知道了
- You just got to get mad. - yeah,got it.
你来试试  揍我
Now you try. hit me.
我想我还是挑个和我长不多的家伙揍吧
Uh,I think I'll stick to just picking on somebody my own size.
试着狠狠地揍我
Hit me as hard as you can.
小家伙  我不会和一个十二岁的小家伙玩拳击游戏
Dude,I'm not gonna do "fight club" with a 12-year-old.
行了啊  别再来了啊
All right,cut it out.
打我啊
Make me.
这个一定要教我们
Whoa. whoa,you got to teach us that.
这就像个万恶之市一样
This looks like "new jack city."
难道就没人发现吗
Can nobody can see this?
也许是恶魔隐形水画得吧  只有往生的人才能看到
Maybe it's demon invisible ink -- only see it in the veil.
知道这是用来干嘛的吗
Any idea what it's for?
就靠我们去查了
We'll find out.
伙计  看我露一手先
Dude,check me out.
知道吗  做一个鬼魂还挺爽的嘛
You know,this ghost thing -- it's -- it's kind of rad.
是铁器
It's iron.
兔崽子们
Boys...
喜欢这地方吗?
...find the place okay?
这下尝到石盐的滋味了吧?
Rock salt's not so much fun anymore,is it?
阿拉斯泰尔
Alastair...
你这混蛋
You bastard.
尽管来啊
Well,go on.
怎么不用你那驱魔术了呢?  自命不凡的小子
Why don't you try some of your mojo on me now,hotshot?
不披着人皮就很难做到吧?
It's hard to get it up when you're not wearing your meat,huh?
滚回地狱去
Go to hell.
我也想嘛
Ah,if only I could,
但他们偏要我到这个冷死人的鬼地方
But they just keep sending me back up to this arctic craphole.
来杀死死神?
To kill death?
不不  是杀两个  这样才能解开封印
No,to kill death twice. it takes two to break a seal.
但我发现了另一个出现的地点
I figured another one would show up,though.
他们简直就像旅鼠一样好对付
They're like lemmings.
顺便  再见到你真高兴 迪恩
By the way,it's,uh,good to see you again,dean.
你想怎么射随便你  但你杀不了我们
You can shoot us all you want,but you can't kill us.
是吗?
Ah,that so?
月方上正中
Moon's in the right spot.
舞台已铺就
The board is set.
让我们好戏开场吧?
Let's get started,shall we?
你就用这玩儿杀死神吗?
You're gonna kill a reaper with that?
不觉得有些蠢吗?
It's little on the nose,don't you think?
真的?
Is it?
一个老朋友借给我的
An old friend lent it to me.
要知道  虽然他不是骑白马的
You know,he doesn't really ride a pale horse,
但他也有三个伙伴(对比天启四骑士, 分别骑白红黑绿马)
But he does have three amigos.
而他们都很热衷于末日审判
And they're just jonesing for the apocalypse.
总得照顾一下底下的伙伴  你说呢?
Pays to have friends in low places,don't you think?
Hic cruor messorius,illud sigillum,quod luciferem reverendum obstringit,
Aperiat ut resurgat!
Wind gusting no!
不!  住手!
Stop!
Hic cruor messorius...
我知道你在这儿
I know you're here.
怎么了  你这臭东西
What's the matter,you reeking son of a bitch?
怕了女人了?
You afraid of a skirt?
你这混蛋
Vis,vis -- ah! son of a bitch!
Illud sigillum,quod luciferem reverendum obstringit,aperiat ut resurgat!
再见了
Bye-bye.
你弟弟呢?
Where's your brother?
我去找他  你快离开这儿
I'll go find him. you get out of here.
Animum vult decipi,ergo...
帕梅拉
Pamela!
你笑什么?
What's so funny?
我不能死  至少不该死在这儿
I can't die -- not in this town.
听着
Look.
-帕梅拉  -少担心了  坏家伙
Pamela -- quit your worrying,grumpy.
给我弄瓶酒来吧?
How about you make me a drink,huh?
你得去医院
You need a doctor.
给我弄瓶酒来 萨姆
Make me a drink,sam.
你跑不了的...迪恩
You can't run...dean.
逃不出我的手心
Not from me.
我就是缠绕在你内心的小小恐惧源
I'm inside that angst-y,little noggin of yours.
搞什么?
What the hell?
你说呢
Guess again.
你和萨姆刚保住了一个封印
You and sam just saved a seal.
而我们抓住了阿拉斯泰尔
We captured alastair.
迪恩 这是一场胜利
Dean,this was a victory.
是啊  但别指望我谢你
Well,no thanks to you.
为什么这么说?
What makes you say that?
你一直都在?
You were here the whole time?
自始至终都在
Enough of it.
我们被石盐折磨的时候你在哪儿?
Well,thanks for your help with the rock salt.
我们无法破解葬礼屋的符号
That script on the funeral home -- we couldn't penetrate it.
还有天使做不到的事情吗?
That was angel-proofing?
不然我干嘛开始求助你们?
Why do you think I recruited you and sam in the first place?
是你求助我们的?
You recruited us?
打电话给你们的不是鲍比 迪恩
That wasn't your friend bobby who called,dean.
他也没有告诉萨姆有关封印的事
It wasn't bobby who told sam about the seal.
那是你?
That was you?
如果你需要我们帮忙  干嘛他妈不直说?
If you want our help,why the hell didn't you just ask?
因为你总是和我对着干
Because whatever I ask,you seem to do the exact opposite.
那现在呢?
So,what now,huh?
这个镇上的人还是会死吗?
The people in this town,they just gonna start dying again?
是的
Yes.
他们都是好人
These are good people.
你就不能破例几次吗?
What,you think you can make a few exceptions?
万物注定轮回
To everything there is a season.
对我你就破了例
You made an exception for me.
你是与众不同的
You're different.
迪恩?
Dean?
我可以帮你
I could use your help.
你好 科尔
Hey,cole.
不管怎样  和你弟弟说声谢谢
Tell your brother thanks for nothing.
看看她吧  Cole
Look at her,cole.
意识到她有多么痛苦吗?
Do you see how unhappy she is?
所以我才想留在她身边
That's why I want to stay with her.
只要她依然能感觉到你  她就会一直痛苦下去 因为她放不下你
As long as she can feel you,she'll be in pain,because she can't let go,
因为你也放不下她
Because you won't let go of her.
为何从没人告诉我那个世界是怎样的?
Why won't anybody tell me what's on the other side?
可能因为这样你就没有惊喜了
Maybe nobody wants to ruin the surprise.
这不算答案
That's not an answer.
她不会给你答案的  Cole
She won't answer you,cole.
死神从不会
Reapers never do.
但是相信我...
But trust me...
呆在这儿比另一个世界更糟
Staying here is a whole lot worse than anything over there.
为什么?
Why?
总有一天  你的家人都会去世
Because one day,your family will be gone,
对你来说就一无所有了
And there will be nothing left here for you.
害怕是正常的
It's okay to be scared.
我没有害怕
I'm not scared.
我们都会害怕
We're all scared.
你不知道吧
That's the big secret.
所有的人都会害怕
We're all scared.
你也会来吗?
Are you coming?
我肯定会比你预料的要早来
Oh,i'm sure I'll be there sooner than you think.
留心那个孩子
Look out for that boy.
你要小心自己 迪恩
Look out for yourself,dean.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我经历过很多次死前临别
I've been around death from the get-go.
知道我见过最多的是什么吗?
You know what I see most?
谎言
Lies.
"他会去到一个更好的地方"
"he's in a better place."
"不管怎样  他们终于在一起了"
"at least they're together now."
你一直在骗自己 迪恩  因为如你所说  地狱深渊
You all lie to yourselves,dean,'cause like you said,deep down,
你只有恐惧
You're all scared.
别再骗自己了 迪恩
Stop lying to yourself,dean.
什么?
What?
天使们救了你
The angels have something good in store for you...
给了你第二次生命
A second chance.
不是吗?
Really?
因为我很确定...
'cause I'm pretty sure...
你知道在地狱...
Deep down...
深渊尽头的那令人骨悚然的东西
You know something nasty's coming down the road.
相信你的直觉 迪恩
Trust your instincts,dean.
世间本无奇迹
There's no such thing as miracles.
你想说什么?
What are you saying?
Imum vult decipi,ergo decipiatur.
中文字幕
Vis,vis,vis.
我们去和泰莎谈谈
Hey,we just got to talk to tessa,
只要让她推迟一下  这样我们就能治好你
That's all -- get her to hold off reaping till we get you better.
我肯定她现在已经开始了
I'm pretty sure she's started up again.
怎么了?
What happened?
泰莎呢? 迪恩
Dean,where's tessa?
她已经...
She's...
-帕梅拉 我很抱歉  -闭嘴
Pamela,i'm so sorry. stop.
-你不该沦落至此的  -没错
You don't deserve this. yeah,i don't.
我早说了我不想被牵扯进来
I told you I didn't want anything to do with this.
帮我个忙好吗?
Do me a favor?
让那个混蛋鲍比 辛格见鬼去!
Tell that bastard bobby singer to go to hell for
他之前干嘛要介绍你们给我认识
Ever introducing me to you two in the first place.
放松 帕梅拉
Take it easy,pamela.
你会去到一个更好的地方的 如果这算安慰的话
If it's any consolation,you're going to a better place.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
不过管他呢
But what the hell,right?
每个人迟早都会死
Everybody's got to go sometime.
过来这边
Come here.
我知道你对那个恶魔的所作所为 萨姆
I know what you did to that demon,sam.
我能感觉到你的内心深处
I can feel what's inside of you.
如果你还认为这是出于好意 再考虑看看
If you think you have good intentions,think again.
帕梅拉?
Pamela?
帕梅拉!
Pamela!
她对你说了什么?
What did she say to you?
[谨以此季献给Kim Manners]